

Blake Hall

UX designer and content strategist with a background in marketing and community management. Skilled at collaborating with development teams, performing and presenting user research, finding product solutions, developing prototypes and user flows, and creating copy to match the brand voice.

Open to Relocation & Remote Work

Houston, TX (956) 802-3412 blakedanielhall@gmail.com https://www.blakeonux.com linkedin.com/in/blakedhall

SKILLS

UX Design User

User Testing

Prototyping

Copywriting

User Research

Leadership

Relationship Management

Project Management

TOOLS

Figma

User Personas

Balsamiq

Google Suite

Adobe XD

User Research

EDUCATION

CareerFoundry
July 2020 - May 2021
UX Design Program

TCU Fort Worth, TX B.A. Advertising

WORK EXPERIENCE

UX Design & Content Strategy Consultant

Remote · October 2020 - Present

· Consult with businesses to help them improve digital products

Audience Development Coordinator, Funimation

Flower Mound, TX / Remote • October 2019 - October 2020

 Designed and maintained calendar tool for team to track hundreds of branded social media posts each week

Associate Community Manager, Blizzard Entertainment Irving, CA • July 2015 - February 2019

- Managed daily user research for Diablo III, a multi-million user franchise, from gathering feedback, to collaborating with development, to relaying product changes to users
- Improved development team's understanding of and confidence in user research by overhauling feedback process to create a five point severity ranking system for user issues
- Partnered with internal stakeholders to improve lines of feedback and communication between company and users

PROJECTS

CareerFoundry, Student

Remote • July 2020 - Present

- Developed app prototype over 24-hour period with three other students at Clinhacks 2021. Goal: Keep people safe from high-risk locations for disease. Result: won Kuzoclass prize for "Most Feasible Business Idea." Tools: Figma & Google API. View prototype.
- Designed webapp as a beginning-to-end UX design project. Goal: Help tattoo enthusiasts find the perfect artist. Methods: User research, prototyping, design, user testing, and high-fidelity prototyping. Tools: Adobe XD, Figma, Balsamiq. <u>View prototype.</u>
- View the complete case studies for these and more here